Ah, okay. It works. Okay, it works.
I'm sorry for the sudden scream. My mic
was not emitting on stream.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. How's
everyone doing?
Hello.
Uh, so today we will be playing Warog.
It's Warog time. It's Warog.
War dogs. War dogs. War dogs. War dogs.
[laughter]
Why scream war dogs? What the hell? Um,
one second. I chose the wrong bit rate.
One second.
6,000. So, official.
It's a bit finicky. Uh, thought so.
Yesterday, I tested this. So, you guys
know why um my quality of my streams are
bad because I'm multi streaming, right?
So apparently I recently figured it out
that I was sending 3,000 bit rate to my
to like Sydney servers
because my since I'm in Japan close to
Tokyo uh or maybe not close that close
to Tokyo. So apparently
Japan uh my internet connection from
Japan sending [music]
data to Sydney takes like around uh
round trip of like 216
milliseconds.
So that's why I'm stuck with this 3,000
bit rate for my streams. So apparently I
switched to a different service uh
Singapore like old service I've been
using for the longest time and then I
switched to a freeear one. So
uh right now I believe the bit rate is
still 3,000 but but there's a but yes uh
but you will I'll be able to send 6,000
bit rate like the basic 6,000 bit rate.
Um
uh I'm sending it to like Singapore
servers. So that feed is sending sent to
Sydney servers. So it uh publishes to
every other platforms. So it's like a
big of a small little roundrip uh kind
of hack I guess but some it works kind
of.
[music]
Uh,
but yeah, it should work. All right.
Anyhow, with that said, um,
I'm excited for dogs. Before I start the
stream, I just want to say something.
Okay.
Hello, Cyber. Oh, wait, wait. That's
old. Sorry. Um, thank you for the
subscri subscription on YouTube. Cyber
Cyber Disc Jo 33. Thank you. Thank you.
Nice.
So, uhah.
Okay. So, today we'll going be playing
Wars. Yeah. And there's drops enabled on
Twitch. If you're watching my stream on
Twitch, feel free to like grab all the
uh all the drops as you can. Yeah. If
I'm ending my stream, feel free to watch
another war dog streamer to grab your
Warogs drops. You need to watch like 16
hours or something. Like that's like you
have to watch them for a long time to
get all the drops. I already have done
it. I already have all the drops.
[laughter]
But yeah, man, I feel so happy and like
hyper today. Huh? Weird. But yeah, so
it's currently 9:39. I will be eating my
dinner by 11 or something. I don't know,
but I'm planning to eat my dinner by
around that time. Um yeah, I just wanted
to talk a little bit before we continue
to watch dogs. Uh so yeah, so um lately
I've been testing testing testing all
the things on my PC.
My laptop I bought uh gaming laptop I
bought from Japan. Uh this what is it
called? Uh next gear laptop I have not
next. I actually actually thought it was
next but it's not it's a music software
thingy. Next but yeah um next scale
laptop I have it's 16 GB. It's a
bottleneck but it can play games well.
Good quality etc. 5060 uh GPU, right?
5060 RTX, it can run well, etc. Good,
good, good. But
while gaming and streaming, it is
causing issues, right? I realized that
my laptop cannot handle both gaming and
streaming all together.
Dara,
I thought um it's not going to happen
anytime soon or maybe it could or not
now, but probably next month or maybe
next next month or maybe next year, who
knows? But my plan is to bring my old PC
for which is lonely over there in India
back my back in my home. Okay, I'm
planning to get my PC from India back to
uh back like transfer like Korea it all
the way to Japan so I can have it run as
a streaming PC, you know. So, I'm going
to like it has a Ryzen 5 the uh 5600X
and uh GTX 1660 super and a media live
gamer 4K. That is the capture card. So
just like we used to have the show like
long ago if you remember I had I used to
have a dual PC setup. All of my streams
were higher quality 1440p
but um yeah my 2060 uh uh RTX 2060
couldn't handle too much in the in the
end it died to the game called Body Cam
which I streamed a few weeks ago. Uh
right. But but here I was able to stream
body cam right with this laptop I have.
I was able to stream I was able to play.
We played a lot of the new update right.
Yeah. [music] And that's crazy the show.
Yeah. And coming back to the topic. So,
I'm thinking of uh switching this laptop
into a dedicated gaming and main PC
thingy and having my old setup act as a
encoding session for YouTube, Twitch,
and Kick all those platforms. I will use
multireaming thingy too, but also I want
to send like [music] what I want to send
like a good quality uh high FPS gameplay
feed to you guys so I can provide you
good quality content and everything.
Yeah. So [snorts]
that also requires good call it good bit
rate. Now so many things there's so much
to dabble into. I really wish what I
expect and what I'm thinking of happens.
Well somehow I can get my uh system
stuff back here if that is possible. Now
oh boy I can like do so much.
One would say, "Jac, why can't you build
a PC from here in Japan? There's a lot
of used uh secondhand shops here in
Tokyo and stuff. You can just build it,
right?" Yes, I plan to do that too. Um
like I was thinking isn't it better if
to reuse my hardware I have back home
which will be long forgotten and not
being you not be used rather than
getting rather than making it rot and be
broken over time or get word wear down
uh over time I could bring it here set
it up uh maintain it etc patch it up fix
it up use it for my stuff All right. Is
that's Isn't that better?
Yeah. Lately, I've been like gaming.
I've been I have not turned off my
laptop for one week. I'm using it as a
PC, bro. I have not turned off my laptop
for one week. I did turn it off and
restart it today just for stream. There
was a Windows update. I hope it won't
break stuff. But yeah, [snorts] I've
been lately been using Apollo and Arus
to like uh which is equivalent to
Moonlight and uh Sunshine to like uh
like stream your PC to over the internet
or your play locally on your devices
like uh like n like steam deck steam
deck or like phone and stuff like
portable devices. So, I've been using
that to like play War Dogs and other
games and control my PC and play with
that uh virtual Xbox controller thingy
buttons and like play games and stuff
and it's been really nice. I can't play
properly with mouse and keyboard kind of
setup, but but
um at least I can AFK. [laughter]
At least I can AFK and get some money in
Warogs. Did you know you can AFK and
like No, you should not AFK. If you are
AFK gang in a APC truck, the spawn
vehicle,
[clears throat] as long as the spawn
vehicle is alive and healthy and does
not die, you can AFK the whole thing and
gain like around like what um straight
up 50 uh 500,000k
like 5,000
dollars per per game. Wink. uh if
everything goes well. But yeah, I had
bad moments. Uh died. My teacher caught
me gaming and I got scolded. Ah, too
much things happened.
Ah, too much things happened. But I'm
having fun. Vardox is always fun. It's
crazy. It's a good game. Love it.
Yeah,
wild dogs is always fun.
Anyone? Oh, I yapped so much the show.
Hi. Uh, let me set up the stuff and we
can switch to the game scene.
All right,
let me connect my chat stuff so I can
like see you guys.
my uh before I re I want to reconnect
and give uh 66,000 bit rate. Okay. BRB 3
2 the stream will be disconnected in
three
two
a one
and a zero.
Okay, we should be back. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Can you hear me? Okay. Hi.
The stream is back online. Let's go.
Yay.
Kim show. It's back. It's back. Yay. Hi.
We are on 6,000 bit rate. So, you will
experience good quality. Good quality.
[music] And let me double check my
thingy. I'll just remove my old clock.
Put the new uh 1 second. I just want to
uh measure the latency, so to speak.
Give me a minute.
Just want to measure the latency. Uh 05.
What's it over here?
It should be round trip should be like
14.
Let me watch myself on Twitch. That's
better.
Munos.
So there is approximately a 6second
delay and that's normal
so to speak. Yeah, that's normal.
Normal. Normal.
Hi.
Switch to that.
It's Warog time.
Okay. Close my browser. I need my X FPS
as much as possible.
Hello.
Good evening. How's doing?
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Okay, it's water dogs time. Let's go.
Good evening.
What the dogs?
Let me put my phone. Actually, I was in
the rain earlier.
I went out. It was raining. My phone got
wet. I couldn't charge it. Moisture
thingy. I had to use some online
website. Use that sound and everything
to like get off the get the water off of
my charging port and speaker. It worked
somehow. But yeah.
How are you, Jo? I'm doing great. I'm
high energy today. I'm going to eat. I'm
hungry. I'm going to eat dinner in like
1 hour from now. Uh or like 30 minutes
or something.
But yeah.
Oh yeah, there's a uh there's a
community server. Uh Japan JP. Uh let's
see if it if it is open.
Uh
Candy Gaming.
Ah, there's so many people. I don't
think I can get in. Can I get in?
There's so many people, bro. Come on.
I want to get in. The thing is now the
Asia ser Asia E server is hoardered by
these Chinese players. They have their
own servers and this and that. It's so
crazy, man. Like I feel like it's better
for me to uh go uh play with like
Americans like NA server or something. I
want to talk with Japanese people and
like get uh like you know um interact
with people cuz I'm a I'm a baka who
barely interact with people and
I don't know
it's it's rough man over here.
Let's uh go to 66. No, maybe six. Maybe
95. No, 88. 301. Okay, let's go. We're
going here
301.
Hello.
Evening.
Why I got kicked out?
You let me in, brother.
Let me in.
I think I should join a server which is
not growing yet. 392 maybe. How you
doing, Jo? I'm doing amazing. I'm doing
good. Good. I got to eat soon.
Yeah,
I'm happy cuz I'm going to play Warog.
much energy buffering.
It's buffering. Nh
my internet. H of course it's buffering.
>> Oh no it's buffering.
Yada yada yada yada. It's buffering.
Oh god it's buffering.
Oh no, it's Bang.
How are you doing, Jock? I'm doing
amazing. Dorja,
hope you're doing well.
One second. I have to log to the server.
What you going to eat? Uh my roommate
going made a biryan uh uh like uh fish
curry
fish curry and stuff
authentication code
hydra me.
I'm going to eat. Someone bought a tank
already, bro.
Okay,
man. Everyone is like grinding this
game. It has reached to the point that
these grinders have reached like the end
game. They're unlocking stuff already.
Okay. Is my stream okay now? It's not
okay. It's not buffering anymore, but
the quality is bad.
Oh god.
Oh lord. The delay is insane.
Yeah, the delay is insane.
I did not expect that.
>> You want it? You got to spend money to
make money.
What is it this time?
Okay, I'm going to go with this. Take
one mag
and some
lose ammo
and uh get five thing.
And a parachut
>> later bon up petit for later. Yes. Enjoy
your fish curry. Yeah. Fish curry and
like basmati rice, red slam peas, green
peas and stuff. All those stuff. It's
literally a biryani mix you can say.
So, for today's stream, I'm going to be
a driver. Uh, I don't know whose car is
this.
What are they doing?
Delay is not fixed. It's 600.
Uh,
wait. What do I do to fix this?
I thought
streaming to Singapore are very well
helped, but proof.
Why?
It'll it'll fix. Oh my god.
What is happening here?
I'm stuck inside it.
Oh my lord.
What is happening? Do you see this?
What are they doing?
Oh my god.
Okay, today we are going to be a truck
driver.
>> No found what you're after yet.
>> Oh, I can buy this.
Or should I go uh level up my stuff?
See you around.
You're back.
>> Need money, you know.
Damn son.
>> So, let's uh plan out what we need to
do. Okay. I want to get recon. Wait, I
can also get I can also get driver
thingy too.
Um,
let's see what we need. Uh, my
teammates, what do they need? There's
two bases.
Uh, which is main? I don't know.
Both are bringing supplies, right? Why
did Where's the tower, brother? What the
hell? What are they doing? What's the
blue team doing?
What's the blue team doing? If they're
Oh my god. Oh my lord. Okay, someone put
a fob here. What is going on? What are
they doing? Are they fighting fighting?
Okay, if they're fighting fighting, I'll
just get like They're fighting fighting.
I'll just get that corn. You buy it.
>> I just got uh just get um this thing.
>> Get out of there.
>> Okay,
now the question is how will I go? The
my ride is gone.
Wait, there's a free truck over there. I
I can take it
perhaps.
Oh, that truck is here.
Please tell me it's not locked. Please
tell me it's not locked. It's not
locked. I'm going to steal it.
Build supply.
I'm going to steal it.
Let's go.
Ah. Ah. Ah. Oh. Oh. My super super cool
driving skills. I survived the
You don't talk about that. Okay.
Wow.
Wait, why is it
drifting so much?
Also guys,
um
I think the delay is a bit too much.
Um
should I restart the stream?
It should be catching up by now. Like
it's literally
um like a second behind.
Like you're like literally behind
behind. Literally are like 15 seconds 20
seconds behind. That's it.
That's your name.
What?
Oh. Oh. Super skills. Super skills come
to the handy. Okay. Nice.
Oh,
this truck has been going through a lot
due to me.
Oh my goodness.
Why am I climbing mountains with this
truck?
I can see a half tower over there.
Not again. I think it's okay, isn't it?
Uh you're behind by two three two
minutes.
Let me stop uh pause it over here as in
let me keep my stream stuck till here
till you guys catch up. I'm going to
restart the feed. Okay.
The slope is so pain. I'll just
Wait,
is my internet this bad today? What the
hell?
This doesn't make sense.
Why?
Oh, I was speaking so much. No one heard
me. Okay. I was saying like
I feel like someone's eating my
internet,
not my phone. Then who is it?
Wow.
Ah, the bridge rate is bad. I hate this.
Why? Yeah.
Man, I hate this. Okay, let's play for a
bit.
I feel like the game is eating up half
of the internet. That's why.
What?
Ah, there's an enemy helicopter.
I got you, fam.
I got you. I got you. I got you. M here.
[\h__\h]
Oh my god, I'm dying over here. I need
to go back home.
I did my job. It's on you guys. Oh god,
I can't even drive.
Oh my god. This This vehicle is going to
explode any moment, man.
Hey,
what did I do?
What did I do to make it this bad?
I wonder.
Okay,
so apparently my internet is bad because
half of the internet is getting eaten by
the game,
which is bad. But yeah,
uh
hello solar um hello solar.
Welcome.
Oh my god, I did not see that.
A little bit more though. You can do it.
Don't die on me. I know my tire is
busted,
but still. A little bit more though.
It's over there.
You got this.
Believe.
Oh my god. It's not even moving much. I
think the front tire is but busted.
Oh yeah, it is busted.
Oh, wait. The tire is small. It's
supposed to be big.
Oh no.
Oh, did I did I like Oh god, that's bad.
There's a broken helicopter over here.
Oh my lord.
Okay.
M
okay. My truck is fixed.
Either I can keep doing the truck or
I could scout the enemies and help
revive these guys
maybe,
right?
I don't know.
Shimmer B.
I have to do something about my stream
though.
You guys are
guys are stuck at like but then
It's my first time driving the APC.
Let's give it a try.
like driving the APC also gives you
bonus you know
It's super slow.
Okay.
Gumbar.
Wait, how do you turn on the
Spawn on me. Spawn on me. Spawn on me.
Make me money.
Uh, where is my team going?
Okay, two people are coming in.
Feel free to spawn. Okay, they spawned
on me. Oh, I'm getting money.
Let's go aggressive. Okay.
Let's
go aggressive.
go. We got a capture.
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he?
Fired on. I'm approaching your position.
I'm so sorry.
Why is my paying so bad?
build up for additional threats.
Oh my god.
Where are they shooting from? Oh.
and Tai Beam.
Hold on.
[\h__\h] you. [\h__\h] you. [\h__\h] you, [\h__\h]
Ah, I swear.
Why is my streamed pain?
Why is my stream so pain?
Bro,
brother, this is not supposed to work
happen.
Low quality and everything, bro.
Dream dying brother. Come on.
Oh my god.
>> Hold on. I'm inbound.
Broccoli, I got you.
Thank you.
Who's shooting from top though?
I don't get it.
Everyone has a hecker.
Wait, they took
they took the tower
again.
Oh, took the tower again.
[\h__\h]
The chopper is
a location.
[laughter]
>> Nice.
Crazy.
>> QUICK.
Many
people are getting in like that.
Where are the rest of the people?
I don't see anyone.
Was that a snip?
They could be sniping me. Who knows?
All my demons are dying over there.
>> [panting]
>> I got sniped from here.
The game is going to end. I don't want
to
drive him now.
I could just try my luck on her,
I suppose.
How are they fighting? What? Where?
I'm in the ground.
Go go go go go.
What?
Wow, this is bad, bro.
Why is my internet so bad today?
Did I fix it? No, I did not fix that.
[\h__\h]
Yeah. [crying]
Bro,
don't do this to me.
Why? Today was a good day. Don't ruin
today.
Today was a good day.
Why?
Why are you so mean to me,
brother Christ? Why?
Oh god, the stupid internet.
Anything everything other than streaming
you work.
Why today? Bro, brother
brotherh.
This sucks, brother. This duck style.
This sucks. This sucks so much.
internet wi-i
Damn.
Shouldn't have touched my thingy.
I shouldn't have touched thingy.
Now you're a stable.
Wow.
Now you're stable. Wow.
Now he's stable now.
9 second delay. Now you're back to
normal, bro.
I want to just rip everything off, bro.
Uh-huh.
I still What did I do?
was checking
the obvious stuff, right?
Wow.
My internet is bad. Really bad today.
It is really bad today. I feel like
it definitely is bad.
It definitely is bad today. Like
Singapore show should be working though,
but
it's not sending feed.
Uh,
whatever.
I am done it.
Uh zero tier
even connect to the my database,
bro. Wow.
The game is still fetching in game data.
Let me close the game maybe.
What is happening brother?
I was enjoying it. Was a good thing. The
wife was so great. Then this stupid
thing had to happen. Comfort.
Uh
I can't join any network. Why?
What happened today?
Like, did something happen?
Okay, we should be good. I think I fixed
mine and then I suppose
um Can you guys hear me?
Okay,
I'mma change the feed to six.
Um
6,000
bit rate. What happens? Okay. 3 2 1.
I shouldn't have changed it. Oh,
my wifi could hates me.
My Wi-Fi couldn't hate me.
Why are you acting up like this? Be a
good boy.
Why do you want to
Why?
Rest in pieces though.
H. This is so bad.
It works. It doesn't works. It works. It
doesn't works. It works. It doesn't
works. What is going on?
I
dynamic DDNS UNP is enabled.
DMZ
uh port forwarding is enabled
update is not there. Others
sim card management.
What? Metro jewels.
Ah.
What should I do to fix this?
Uh
let's see
world.co
Cool.
Bad address.
HTTPS.
Maybe Sydney would work.
that said me
master lab
go
slash life
bad address
and Maybe
indicator lights.
I want to know what is going on right
now. Communication mode is SD.
Operator network. Wi-Fi is on. Okay.
Modified lawyer
access. Okay. Only my PC is using this
then. None there.
Restricted mode.
Okay. Wi-Fi settings. Single society.
VPS. Everything is nice and good. Why
was it more consist
when there is a way
Huh?
[\h__\h]
Should I change it to hybrid mode?
Maybe.
No, I should not. I totally start.
H okay.
I
Okay, you know what? BRB. I'll go eat.
Take get something to eat and come back
and mess around with this.
We are way
everyone.
Okay, I'm back finally. I am so so so so
sorry for making you guys wait for so
long.
So it seems my internet is bad.
It seems as far as I can see.
It seems my internet is really bad.
I don't know what to do. I really do
want to play,
but also I feel like I should quit.
This is what I was saying in the
beginning of the stream. Like
like when did the internet start to
break? the moment I launched the game,
right? I was able to talk and have fun
in the beginning of the stream. Oh,
wait. The thing is still stinging. One
second.
Uh,
there you go.
I was able to do a lot
on like uh talk and stuff on today's
stream,
but well
uh
delete that.
I don't know what to do honestly if you
ask me.
This internet issue is such a problem.
Like even if I get like a a dual PC
setup, like a streaming PC, if I get my
PC stuff done,
how will I even know? I don't I I don't
I'm not even planning to buy a monitor.
How will I even know if my internet
died? How will I know if my bit rate is
bad? This is such a headache,
honestly.
21.
Like I don't
get it. Just don't get it. Just simply
don't get it.
Like
Like why the upload speed you're
blocking?
Could have done anything else.
Huh?
Papa.
>> [singing]
[singing]
>> Communication was flash independently on
the connection speed.
It's not flashing. It's lights on and
it's blinking.
What should I do? What should I do? What
should I do? What should I do?
It's not on plus area mode. So, there's
that.
Oh,
like I have 100 MB upload, bro. No. Uh,
like download like why is my upload so
damn low? Come on, brother. Why are you
3 Mbps?
I'm raging. I just want to play. I
wanted to play the game
and I'm stuck with my stupid internet
providing me with bad internet
today.
Wow.
Crazy. Crazy.
Crazy.
No.
I know. The moment I end the stream, it
it will revert back to normal.
I I I absolutely know
it will revert.
How do I run a speed pas against uh
>> [singing and music]
[groaning and screaming]
>> this stupid thing. It does not let me
go up for a sing
or
okay let's say from here to Singapore
how much delay is it I'm curious it
should work
yeah
Let's go to
100. Yeah. Download
three.
Now the game changer guy.
Ah, it's 1 MB upload. That's why my
internet is bad. Ah,
my upload to Singapore is bad. D.
Ow.
This AU
AU internet is so pain
you on that
nana
we couldn't enjoy today's stream. I'm
I'm sorry people
guys would have wanted you guys came in
enjoying and expect good stream.
It's going to be 12. You know what?
Let's end today. Even though I couldn't
do much
failure cuz of internet con, but it is
what it is,
man. It sucks.
Are you serious? Right. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I was like I pressed something and the
internet was like back to normal.
Okay. It's actually now No. Is it
actually fixing? Is it because it's
12:00? It's going to be 12. Is it
because it's going to be 12? Is in my
internet coming back online?
Is it getting fixed right now just
because it's going to be 12? Bruh.
How dare you?
Why do I have a feeling it is it is
fixing itself, right? Just because it's
12. Oh my god. At this point, I should
just stream at 12. Bro, what the hell?
At this point, I should just stream from
12 to like 3:00 a.m. or something.
Are you serious?
Wait, it's actually
showing sign fixing.
What?
Bro, the up
MB 13 MB. Are you kidding me? Are you
kidding me? Internet,
bro. I was here to play.
No way. It actually fixed itself.
No, no, no, no, no. It's going up and
down. [laughter]
It's going up and down. Nand
[crying]
I wanted to play.
You know what? I think I'll just play
off stream.
This is just sad. Everyone, this is just
sad. This is honestly sad. Like my
internet is like, "Okay,
okay, I I'll make you work as long as
it's 12 a.m.
It's stabilizing itself." Like wait, let
me put my
stream is 3,000.
stream rate trade is 3,500
kbps and that's 3.5 MB
and I'm currently having a the upload
upload speed from Japan to Singapore
which is similar to the server I'm
streaming to
um of 7 MP upload. It's supposed to give
enough.
I don't have anything else running on
this
except OBS right now. [music] And wow,
the audacity of fixing itself. And now
you're full grain.
Brah.
Okay, you know what? We are ending the
stream. It's going up and down. It's
actually going up and down.
But yeah, thank you to everyone who came
by today. I'm so sorry. It was like um
all over the place. But yeah, thank you
to Aditi for coming by. Rashavan, thank
you for coming by. Kali, thank you for
coming by. And um uh who else came?
Alisa, thank you for coming by.
Alisa, thank you for coming by. And
those who were lurking,
all the lurkers, thank you for coming
by. Those who are watching this board
back again, thank you.
Have a good one everyone.
If you do see me go live on kick or
something or Twitch or something, don't
mind it. I'm just testing.
to see if this stupid thingy works
after I end my stream. Of course, I know
it's going to work. I know it will
[music] work. But yeah, anyhow, good
night. I'm going to end I'll stream uh
maybe next time. Next stream will be on
Saturday, maybe. Who knows if I can
stream tomorrow and day after cuz by
this time I'll be coming back home after
work tired. I eat some dinner and then
I'll be like going to sleep or something
or I could stay for two hours
like right now and then uh head to bed.
Who knows? But yeah, thank you for
today. Good night everyone. Have a good
one.
Why did I
mo